https://gentechscientific.com/content/7-privacy-policy

Cookies | Privacy Policy     Shop Our eBay Store
Call us: (585) 492-1068 Mon-Fri 8am-4:30pm EST
MENU Inventory Browse CategoriesBrowse ManufacturersSpecialsAnalytical PartsEquipment WantedView All InventoryRequest Quote Product QuoteService QuoteParts RequestSell Your EquipmentPurchase with Trade-InSell / Trade Sell / Trade InstrumentsInstruments WantedCustomer Service Service & Repair Depot RepairWarranty ServiceService AgreementsPreventative MaintenanceParts RequestService RequestTrainingInstallationPacking & DeliveryRefurbishment ProcessFinancing Financing OptionsRentalsAbout About UsCareersCompany NewsProduct LiteratureTestimonialsContact Contact UsEmail Sign-Up Inventory
»Browse CategoriesBrowse ManufacturersSpecialsAnalytical PartsEquipment WantedView All Inventory Request Quote
»Product QuoteService QuoteParts RequestSell Your EquipmentPurchase with Trade-In Sell / Trade
»Sell / Trade InstrumentsInstruments Wanted Customer Service
»Service & RepairDepot RepairWarranty ServiceService AgreementsPreventative MaintenanceParts RequestService RequestTrainingInstallationPacking & DeliveryRefurbishment Process Financing
»Financing OptionsRentals About
»About UsCareersCompany NewsProduct LiteratureTestimonials Contact
»Contact UsEmail Sign-Up
Privacy PolicyGenTech Scientific LLC Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or complete a form from https://gentechscientific.com (the “Site”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:    - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.    - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.    - “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you complete a form through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, address, company name, email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Form Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Form Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Form Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Form Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our forms for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONGoogle AnalyticsWe use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISINGAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt out of targeted advertising by:  COMMON LINKS INCLUDE:    FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads    GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous    BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you complete a form through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, to the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you complete a form through the Site, we will maintain your Form Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.SECURITYPlease note that electronic communication, particularly email, is not necessarily secure against interception. Please do not send sensitive data (e.g., Social Security, bank account, or credit card numbers) by email or web form.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@gentechscientific.com or by mail using the details provided below:23 Mill Street, Arcade, NY, 14009, United States
Categories Buy New Starter Kits Generators Accessories Benches Sampler Systems Gas Chromatography Agilent GC Systems GC Detectors & Inlets GC Autosamplers GC Accessories & Kits GC Installation Kits Mass Spectrometry GC/MS Systems LC/MS Systems Agilent LC/MS Systems Thermo LC/MS Systems Waters LC/MS Systems Orbitrap Systems MS Sample Introduction Mass Spec Accessories MS HPLC Pumps Vacuum Pumps HPLC & UPLC Agilent HPLC Systems PAL HPLC Systems Shimadzu HPLC Systems Dionex HPLC Systems Waters HPLC Systems HPLC Accessories & Kits Inorganic Analysis Ion Chromatography (ICS) ICP & AA Systems ICP Accessories Mass Spec Benches N2 & H2 Generators Niton AnalyzersNitrogen EvaporatorsAll InstrumentsAnalytical Parts Industries & Methods Application Solutions Biological Fluids Cannabis/Medical Marijuana Chemical Clinical Research Drug & Forensic Environmental Food & Beverage Flavor & Fragrance Industrial Hygiene Oil & Gas Pharmaceutical University Instruments
View by ManufacturerAB SciexAgilent TechnologiesDionexShimadzuThermo ScientificWaters All manufacturersAB SciexAgilent TechnologiesBrukerCTC AnalyticsDataApexDionexEdwardsFlomHTALabTechLeyboldOI AnalyticalPerkinElmerPfeifferPowerVarProton OnSiteRestekShimadzuSonationTekmarThermo ScientificUlvacVarianVici/ValcoWaters
LinkedIn Facebook Twitter YouTube JOIN OUR MAILING LIST
Categories All Instruments Gas Chromatography (GC) HPLC/UHPLC Systems Mass Spectrometry (MS) Categories Methods Warranty Options Service & Repairs Refurbishment Process Sales Terms & Conditions Informational Catalogs InformationAbout UsCompany NewsReferral ProgramContact usCareersSitemapChinese SiteSpanish Site GenTech Scientific LLC. 23 Mill Street Arcade, NY 14009. 585-492-1068. info@gentechscientific.com Copyright 2020
